<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bronze VIP Posting Board Archives</title>
<link>http://www.cise.ufl.edu/~hsiao/media/tv/buffy/bronze/</link>
<description>This feed collects the most recent posts for &lt;STRONG&gt;VIP Users&lt;/STRONG&gt; of the various posting boards which cover our favorite Mutant Enemy shows--&lt;EM&gt;Buffy&lt;/EM&gt;, &lt;EM&gt;Angel&lt;/EM&gt;, and &lt;EM&gt;Firefly&lt;/EM&gt;

This syndicated feed only displays the posts as they are culled.  For a more permanent (and more organized) archive, go to &lt;A HREF="http://www.cise.ufl.edu/~hsiao/media/tv/buffy/bronze/"&gt;The Official Site&lt;/A&gt;</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<skipHours><hour>0</hour><hour>1</hour><hour>2</hour><hour>3</hour>
<hour>4</hour><hour>13</hour><hour>14</hour><hour>15</hour>
<hour>16</hour><hour>17</hour><hour>18</hour><hour>19</hour><hour>20</hour>
<hour>21</hour><hour>22</hour><hour>23</hour></skipHours>
<item><pubDate>Fri, 16 Mar 2007 07:15:02 EDT</pubDate>
<title>Bronze Beta Posts as of Fri Mar 16 07:15:02 2007 &amp; Foo</title>
<link>http://www.cise.ufl.edu/~hsiao/media/tv/buffy/bronze/20070315.html</link>
<description>
&lt;DL&gt;&lt;DT&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Christopher Golden&lt;/STRONG&gt; says:&lt;br&gt;
(Wed Mar 14 02:57:12 2007)&lt;/SMALL&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Gahhh!  This five minute rule is for the birds.  :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;While I was writing my post, those others came up.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Beldin, thanks for asking about Jenna.  The series is, at least for the moment, over.  The tenth book was THROAT CULTURE, which I think means you got half way.  Lots of other stuff out there, though.  I've been busy in my time away from Buffy.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Thanks again.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Night.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr noshade size=3&gt;
&lt;a name="VIP002"&gt;

&lt;DT&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Christopher Golden&lt;/STRONG&gt; says:&lt;br&gt;
(Wed Mar 14 02:51:15 2007)&lt;/SMALL&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Carita, let's not worry about colors and such.  I'm just dropping by to say hi.  My VIP time is ancient history.  :)  Though I find I did kind of miss the Bronze.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Christopher Marlowe: Thanks for the vote of confidence.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;And on that note, the long, slow drive-by ends.  I'm wiped.  Btw, like the rest of you, I can't wait for season 8 to start.  I hope Joss does ten more seasons in the comics.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Adios.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr noshade size=3&gt;

&lt;DT&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Christopher Golden&lt;/STRONG&gt; says:&lt;br&gt;
(Wed Mar 14 02:42:58 2007)&lt;/SMALL&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Beldin, thanks.  Good to see you, and some other familiar names as well.  It's been a long time.  :)&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;hr noshade size=3&gt;

&lt;DT&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Christopher Golden&lt;/STRONG&gt; says:&lt;br&gt;
(Wed Mar 14 02:35:36 2007)&lt;/SMALL&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;dd&gt;Hollyn, they're in middle school, and we're doing OLIVER!  It could be a disaster, but with just a few rehearsals under our belts, I'm pretty impressed with the kids.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;a href="BronzeArchive1173839736.htm" style="text-decoration: none"&gt;Previous Posts&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a name="bottom"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;
&lt;/html&gt;
&lt;/DL&gt;</description></item>
</channel></rss>
