<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Bronze VIP Posting Board Archives</title>
<link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today</link>
<description>Atlanta Journal-Constitution Epaper </description>
<language>en-us</language>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77db932b0a0b4007c.html</link><title>9/11 panel delivers 'indictment of FBI'</title><description>
Philip Shenon and Eric Lichtblau - New York Times
Washington --- The FBI came under withering attack on Tuesday by the independent commission investigating the Sept. 11, 2001, attacks, with its chairman describing new staff reports on the bureau's performance before and after the attacks as an ''indictment of the FBI.''    ''It failed and it failed and it failed and it failed,'' commission Chairman Thomas Kean said of the FBI at the public hearing. ''This is an agency that does not work,'' said Kean, the former Republican governor of New Jersey. "It makes you angry. And I don't know how to fix it.''</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c7cd7432b080b900dc.html</link><title>GIs mass at cleric's hide-out</title><description>
Sewell Chan and Thomas E. Ricks - Washington Post
Baghdad, Iraq --- A force of 2,500 troops from three U.S. Army divisions massed Tuesday on the northern outskirts of the Iraqi holy city of Najaf and readied for a confrontation with Shiite Muslim cleric Muqtada al-Sadr, who defiantly declared that he was prepared to die for his cause.     In Washington, the State Department said four mutilated bodies were found west of Baghdad, near where seven U.S. civilians employed by Halliburton Co. vanished Friday during an attack on a convoy. A spokesman said the bodies had not been identified.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d9932b0e199005c.html</link><title>Bush vows America will finish job in Iraq</title><description>
Richard W. Stevenson and Douglas Jehl - New York Times
Washington --- President Bush on Tuesday night strongly reaffirmed his plan to transfer sovereignty in Iraq back to Iraqis on June 30 and said the consequences of failing to follow through on his commitment to bring stability to that nation are unthinkable.     Seeking to tamp down concern that the situation in Iraq is spinning out of control, Bush said he would provide the military with whatever forces it needs to quell the recent surge of violence and come up with whatever money is necessary to rebuild Iraq.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d0932b020de00db.html</link><title>You've got 2 1/2 minutes to prove yourself. ACT!</title><description>
Kathy Janich - Staff
It will be days, possibly months, before Mark Schroeder, a youthful singer-actor from Alpharetta, knows whether 2 1/2 minutes of sweaty, concentrated work this week gets him a paying job.     For 150 seconds Monday, he was front and center in a microcosmic world that will help shape what theater audiences see next year and perhaps in years to come.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d3832b00204002b.html</link><title>CDC to stockpile flu vaccine</title><description>
M.A.J. McKenna - Staff
The Centers for Disease Control and Prevention confirmed Tuesday that it intends to spend $40 million per year in the next two years to stockpile influenza vaccine, hoping to ease the shortages that plagued last winter's flu season.     The policy, first announced Feb. 2 by Health and Human Services Secretary Tommy Thompson, calls for the agency to buy and stockpile 4 million to 6 million doses of flu shots as a potential buffer against spot shortages once the flu season begins.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d5932b0a161002c.html</link><title>Military rejected war game involving Pentagon hit</title><description>
Eric Schmitt - New York Times
Washington --- At least five months before the attacks of Sept. 11, 2001, air defense planners proposed a war-game situation in which a terrorist group hijacked an airliner and flew it into the Pentagon, but the military's Joint Staff rejected the idea, Pentagon officials said Tuesday.    Pentagon officials played down the significance of the proposal, which they said was made at a planning conference for the training exercise in April 2001 and was not based on any specific threat. The exercise was designed to test the military leadership's ability to function at undisclosed locations outside of Washington in an emergency, and the hijacking did not fit the war game's objectives, the officials said.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d0832b0520600fa.html</link><title>U.S.-Israeli link outrages Arabs</title><description>
Margaret Coker - Cox International Correspondent
Jerusalem --- For those concerned with America's image in the Middle East, today's scheduled meeting between President Bush and Israeli Prime Minister Ariel Sharon couldn't come at a worse time.    Images of U.S. soldiers fighting Iraqis last week flooded the Middle East and fueled enraged comparisons of the U.S. military occupation of Iraq to Israel's hold on the West Bank and Gaza Strip.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d5832b0b10c003b.html</link><title>1867 lists among earliest data on Ala. black voters</title><description>
David White - Newhouse News Service
Montgomery --- In faded black ink etched on yellowed paper, cursive handwriting records the names of about 100,000 blacks and 60,000 whites who registered to vote in Alabama in 1867, two years after the Civil War.     The names --- in county-by-county books kept for decades in the Capitol basement and now stored nearby in the state archives --- are some of the earliest listings of the last names of black men in Alabama who had been slaves just a few years before and hadn't had last names.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d7932b0f102003c.html</link><title>NATION IN BRIEF</title><description>
From News Services
New probe launched vs. Jackson ... McCain's wife suffers mild stroke ... Balanced budget tops tax cuts in poll ...</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c7cd6432b0c17b00cc.html</link><title>NATION IN BRIEF: Gay marriage ban on Kentucky ballot</title><description>
From News Services
Kentucky lawmakers have approved a proposed constitutional amendment to ban same-sex marriages, sending the issue to voters. The state Senate, in a 33-5 vote Tuesday, passed the measure, which defines marriage solely as a union between a man and a woman. The proposal also would deny legal recognition of civil unions. The measure will be on the November ballot. The House passed the measure Monday night.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77dc932b0a08d008c.html</link><title>PRESIDENT'S PRESS CONFERENCE: REACTION</title><description>
For the Journal-Constitution
The Atlanta Journal-Constitution invited 200 members of its Voice of Atlanta panel to comment on President Bush's Tuesday night news conference and the issues he discussed. Here are some of their responses: "I am glad to hear that we are going to stay the course, but also am concerned about the price we must pay. I would like to see more countries involved in this war to change the world. . . . I think he did himself some good by coming out and directly answering questions." ... "He seems to think that holding to a course of action, regardless of its effectiveness, is a good thing. And he keeps using the deaths of 9/11 to cover everything he has done. And he can't take any responsibility!" ...</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77dd932b061d5009c.html</link><title>PRESIDENT'S PRESS CONFERENCE: Metro minds not changed . . . Democrats lend an ear, not support</title><description>
Matthew C. Quinn - Staff
Rob and Patricia Friedman, committed Democrats, let President Bush have his say in their DeKalb County living room Tuesday night.      But they said his nationally televised news conference did nothing to change their minds about him or his policies in Iraq.     "It's not going to change anything," said Rob Friedman, 37, executive vice president of a Norcross computer software firm.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77de932b0900c00ac.html</link><title>PRESIDENT'S PRESS CONFERENCE: Metro minds not changed . . . Republicans find Bush reassuring</title><description>
Marlon Manuel - Staff
After listening to President Bush's prime-time news conference Tuesday night, Marietta Republicans Mark and Krista McMichen said their support for continued U.S. involvement in Iraq had solidified.     "It was good he reiterated keeping our commitment" to turn over power to the Iraqis on June 30, said Mark McMichen, 40, who owns a general contracting company. "It gives us a clear objective. It makes people feel more secure about what we're doing."</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d3932b032ed000c.html</link><title>PRESIDENT'S PRESS CONFERENCE: 'There is no safe alternative to resolute action'</title><description>
Associated Press
Text of President Bush's statement on Iraq on Tuesday:      Good evening.     Before I take your questions, let me speak with the American people about the situation in Iraq.     . . . [These have been] tough weeks in that country. Coalition forces have encountered serious violence in some areas of Iraq. Our military commanders report that this violence is being instigated by three groups. Some remnants of Saddam Hussein's regime, along with Islamic militants, have attacked coalition forces in the city of Fallujah. Terrorists from other countries have infiltrated Iraq to incite and organize attacks.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d8732b0f1ee008a.html</link><title>CAMPAIGN WATCH</title><description>
From staff and news services
Bush makes more, pays more . . . ... Applying pressure . . . ... Spinning the Web . . .</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77dc832b0806600ab.html</link><title>DATELINE: BAGHDAD: RESISTANCE IN IRAQ: In Iraq, journalists increasingly in cross hairs</title><description>
Larry Kaplow - Cox International Correspondent
About a year ago here, I was having anguished telephone conversations with my bosses back in the U.S., finally deciding to stay in Baghdad during the bombing that accompanied the American-led invasion.      I was actually safer here then than I am now.      Most of the last year, reporters faced the same dangers as Iraqis. Like the citizens of this nation, reporters were victims of highway banditry. Some were injured in suicide bombings. A few were shot by U.S. troops.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77de832b0316800bb.html</link><title>RESISTANCE IN IRAQ: Foreigners are valued targets</title><description>
Jamal Halaby - Associated Press
Amman, Jordan --- The masked Iraqis, draped in black and armed with automatic rifles and rocket launchers, were looking for one prize when they ambushed the convoy of vehicles: Western passengers.     "They offered us $10,000 for each American passenger, $5,000 for non-Americans, and threatened to kill non-Iraqis," said Haitham Taher, one of 12 Jordanian and Iraqi drivers who escaped Sunday's ambush unharmed in Garma, a village west of Fallujah. "But all our passengers were Iraqis, and we pretended to be Iraqis, so they let us go."</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d7832b0d06e005b.html</link><title>Apathy may depress South African vote</title><description>
Elliott Sylvester - Associated Press
Cape Town, South Africa --- President Thabo Mbeki's African National Congress party is poised to retain --- or even increase --- its sweeping parliamentary majority in today's national election.     While the outcome is certain, political leaders worry that interest in the democratic process is waning a decade after South Africa's first all-race vote ended close to half a century of white minority rule.</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d6832b0f1de004b.html</link><title>WORLD IN BRIEF</title><description>
From News Services
U.S. farmers seek sales to Cuba ... Cheney lauds China on counterterrorism ... Suspected bombers left threats behind ...</description></item>
<item><link>http://www.ajc.com/print/content/epaper/editions/today/news_04c77d4932b0210e001c.html</link><title>CORRECTIONS</title><description>
Staff
&amp;gt;  In Sunday's Metro section obituary on Beverly Shmerling, the professions of two of her sons were reversed. Andrew Bernstein is the senior National Basketball Association photographer, and Richard Bernstein is an internationally known opera singer.</description></item>
</channel></rss>
